<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ian on Ian Worley</title><link>http://www.Ianworley.xyz/authors/ian/</link><description>Recent content in Ian on Ian Worley</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 22:04:21 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.Ianworley.xyz/authors/ian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting the Programmer's Alliance at the University of Central Missouri: A Journey in the Making - Part 1</title><link>http://www.Ianworley.xyz/posts/programming-club-ucm-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 22:04:21 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.Ianworley.xyz/posts/programming-club-ucm-part-1/</guid><description>Starting the Programmer&amp;rsquo;s Alliance at the University of Central Missouri: A Journey in the Making - Part 1 Link to heading As a student of computer science at the University of Central Missouri, I was always searching for ways to dive deeper into the field and improve my skills. During a class discussion about the Association for Computing Machinery workshop on cloud computing, I brought up the idea of starting a programming club with my professor.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>http://www.Ianworley.xyz/posts/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 09:29:10 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.Ianworley.xyz/posts/about/</guid><description>Welcome to my website! My name is Ian Worley and I am a college student at the University of Central Missouri currently in my sophomore year. I am currently majoring in Computer Science.
I have always had a passion for technology and computer programming, and I created this website as a way to share my knowledge and expertise in these fields with others. As a student in computer science, I understand the importance of staying up to date with the latest developments in technology and the constant evolution of programming languages and frameworks.</description></item></channel></rss>